// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q010: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Altona Grocery Store has a good reputation because it carries ------ grown vegetables.',
      choices: ['locality', 'localize', 'local', 'locally'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['locally'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q091',
    },
    {
      question: 'The flooring materials developed by Bellevue Manufacturing are ------ to moisture.',
      choices: ['considerable', 'loyal', 'resistant', 'capable'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['resistant'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q092',
    },
    {
      question: 'A ------ market study is required by Hillside Ad Company’s board of directors before its ambitious business plan is implemented.',
      choices: ['comprehensive', 'comprehend', 'comprehension', 'comprehensively'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['comprehensive'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q093',
    },
    {
      question: 'Due to the successful launch of new products last quarter, ------ employee will receive a special bonus at the end of this month.',
      choices: ['most of', 'most', 'all', 'every'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['every'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q094',
    },
    {
      question: 'During ------, the plant manager noticed something wrong with the conveyor belt on the north side.',
      choices: ['assemble', 'assembled', 'assembles', 'assembly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['assembly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q095',
    },
    {
      question: 'It is widely believed that the quality of sleep, ------ eating habits, has a significant impact on health.',
      choices: ['on behalf of', 'along with', 'in charge of', 'by means of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['along with'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q096',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Daoud is very satisfied with the ------ living room in the Japanese style.',
      choices: ['renovating', 'renovation', 'renovated', 'renovate'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['renovated'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q097',
    },
    {
      question: 'The classical concert next week is expected to draw a ------ number of patrons than last year.',
      choices: ['large', 'largest', 'more largely', 'larger'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['larger'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q098',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Peppin will report to his supervisor about the finance workshop he ------ in Seoul last week.',
      choices: ['will be attend', 'attends', 'is attending', 'attended'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['attended'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q099',
    },
    {
      question: 'Since its establishment, Stellen Group has ------ emphasized customer satisfaction.',
      choices: ['consistency', 'consistently', 'consistent', 'consistence'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['consistently'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題091-100/#q100',
    },
  ],
}